<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Swim England North East</title>
	<atom:link href="http://asaner.org.uk/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://asaner.org.uk</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 18:45:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	
	<item>
		<title>North East Swimmers Continue to Perform in Glasgow</title>
		<link>http://asaner.org.uk/north-east-swimmers-start-with-a-splash-in-glasgow/</link>
				<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 18:40:21 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Small]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Swimming]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://asaner.org.uk/?p=18708</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>Day 4 – Friday 26th July 2019 In Women’s 1500 metres, the first finals event of day 4, City of Leeds Milly Boulding took Silver in the 15 years age group while her team mate Leah Crisp took Gold in the 17/18 years age group. Darlington’s Harriet Rogers followed, taking Silver in the Women’s 100 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk/north-east-swimmers-start-with-a-splash-in-glasgow/">North East Swimmers Continue to Perform in Glasgow</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Day 4 – Friday 26<sup>th</sup> July 2019<br />
</strong>In Women’s 1500 metres, the first finals event of day 4, City of Leeds Milly Boulding took Silver in the 15 years age group while her team mate Leah Crisp took Gold in the 17/18 years age group. Darlington’s Harriet Rogers followed, taking Silver in the Women’s 100 metres Freestyle (15 years) while in the Men’s 100 metres Butterfly, Skipton’s Ned Sharp took Gold (16 years) and City of Leeds Jonathan Milner took Silver (17/18 years).</p>
<p>In 13/14 years Women’s 200 metres Backstroke, Morpeth’s Libby Freeman took Gold while Middlesbrough’s Evie Dilley took Bronze. In the 15 years age group, City of Leeds Kidiest Hodgson took Silver followed by York City’s Ella Stabler who took Bronze and in the 17/18 years age group, City of Sheffield’s Lily Boseley took Gold.</p>
<p>In the last event of the session, the Men’s 4 x 200 metres Freestyle Relay, City of Leeds A Dalton Clapham, Ben Shelton, Ethan Sutcliffe and Akal Rehal took Bronze in the 14/16 years age group followed by City of Sheffield swimmers Elliot Clogg, Eugene Brooks–Clarke, Samuel Budd and Jay Lelliott who took Gold in the 17 years and over age group.</p>
<p><strong>Day 3 – Thursday 25<sup>th</sup> July 2019<br />
</strong>Newcastle Swim Team’s Adam Wilson collected the North East’s first medal of day 3 of the championships with Bronze in the Men’s 17/18 years 1500 metres Freestyle while Borough of Kirklees Jonathan Booth took Bronze in the Men’s MC 100 metres Freestyle.</p>
<p>City of Leeds Isabelle Goodwin took Gold in the Women’s 15 years 200 metres Butterfly followed by Doncaster Dartes Ella Bainbridge who took Silver. In the 16 years age group, City of Leeds Charlotte Robinson took Bronze and her team mate Ciara Schlosshan took Gold in the 17/18 years age group followed by City of Sheffield’s Isobel Grant who took Bronze in the 19 years and over age group.</p>
<p>In the Men’s 100 metres Freestyle, Skipton’s Ned Sharp took Silver in the 16 years age group and in the Women’s 50 metres Freestyle, Darlington’s Harriet Rogers took Silver in the 15 years age group. In the Men’s 400 metres Individual Medley, Borough of Stockton’s William Baines took Gold (13/14 years) and Newcastle Swim Team’s Zak Logue took Bronze (19 years and over).</p>
<p>The Women’s 14/16 years 4&#215;200 metre Freestyle relay saw a close race between City of Leeds (Kidiest Hodgson, Leah Schlosshan, Milly Boulding and Isabelle Goodwin) and Newcastle Swim Team (Lola Davison, Izzy Winter, Amelia Robbertson and Laura), with City of Leeds just touching ahead to take Gold.</p>
<p><strong>Day 2 &#8211; Wednesday 24<sup>th</sup> July 2019<br />
</strong>In the first event of the second day, Derwentside’s Madison Peveller took Silver in the Women’s 13/14 years 100 metres Backstroke. In the same event, City of Leeds Kidiest Hodgson and Newcastle Swim Team’s Amelia Robertson took Silver and Bronze in the 15 years age group while in the 17/18 years age group, City of Sheffield’s Lily Boseley took Silver.</p>
<p>In the Women’s 800 metres Freestyle, Newcastle Swim Teams Laura Hodgson and Lola Davison won Gold in the 13/14 and the 16 years age groups while City of Leeds swimmers Milly Boulding and Leah Crisp won Silver and Gold in the 15 and 17/18 years age groups.</p>
<p>Borough of Stockton’s William Baines took Bronze in the Men’s 13/14 years 200 metres Butterfly, City of Sheffield’s Reuben Visda took Gold in the 16 years age group while in the Women’s 200 metres Breaststroke, City of Sheffield’s Abigail Miles took Silver in the 15 years age as did City of Leeds Rebecca Clynes in the 17/18 years age group.</p>
<p>In the next event, Durham City’s Matthew Cairns took Gold in the Men’s 13/14 years 100 metres Backstroke, Derwentside’s Lewis Maxwell also took Gold but in the 16 years age group and City of Sheffield’s Elliott Clogg took Bronze in the 19 years and over age group.</p>
<p>The Women’s 50 metres Butterfly saw City of Leeds Isabelle Goodwin claim Bronze in the 15 years age group.</p>
<p><strong>Day 1 &#8211; Tuesday 23<sup>rd</sup> July 2019</strong><br />
Today saw the start of the British Swimming Summer Championships 2019 in Toll Cross, Glasgow. Swimmers from across the North East travelled to the Scottish city to compete against others from across the country.</p>
<p>The first medal of the championship for a North East swimmer came from City of Sheffield’s Reuben Visda who took Bronze in the Men&#8217;s 16 years 400 metres Freestyle, this was the followed by a Bronze from his team mate Samuel Budd who took Bronze in the Men’s 19 years and over 400 metres Freestyle. In the next event, the Women’s 200 metres Freestyle, City of Leeds Milly Boulding and Isabelle Goodwin took Gold and Silver in the 15 years age group, Lola Davison from Newcastle Swim Team took Bronze in the 16 years age group and City of Leeds Leah Crisp took Gold in the 17/18 years age group.</p>
<p>In the Women’s 400 metres Individual Medley, City of Leeds Lara Thompson and Leah took Silver and Bronze in the 13/14 years age group while their team mate Kidiest Hodgson took Gold in the 15 years age group.</p>
<p>Durham City’s Matthew Cairns took Gold in the Men’s 13/14 years 50 metres Backstroke, while in the Women’s 50 metres Breaststroke, City of Leeds Rebecca Clynes took Bronze in the 17/18 years age group.</p>
<p>Many congratulations to all the swimmers who have competed so far and best of luck to everyone competing tomorrow.</p>
<p>All the results from the Championships can be <a href="https://www.swimmingresults.org.uk/swimming/results/2019/summerbs/index2.htm?fbclid=IwAR1-Px2E_qDyYfuYEahfc5M0KE6brYnLb1wyOXR7K8Bstp1fa3q34n9mrNA">found here</a> and you can catch all the action from the heats and finals on <a href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC5GyHWsbs7O5m5LohjpKoaQ">British Swimming’s YouTube channel</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk/north-east-swimmers-start-with-a-splash-in-glasgow/">North East Swimmers Continue to Perform in Glasgow</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Have Your Say about Masters Swimming</title>
		<link>http://asaner.org.uk/have-your-say-about-masters-swimming/</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2019 10:54:32 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Daniel Ramm]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Clubs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Masters Swimming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Swimming]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://asaner.org.uk/?p=18734</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>Swim England are currently carrying out an insight (research) focus group on the needs of Masters Swimmers. The North East group will be held in the evening of 12th Sept in Harrogate between 6.30pm and 8.30pm. This is an opportunity for swimmers to shape the future of Masters swimming and swimmers from all backgrounds are [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk/have-your-say-about-masters-swimming/">Have Your Say about Masters Swimming</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Swim England are currently carrying out an insight (research) focus group on the needs of Masters Swimmers. The North East group will be held in the evening of 12th Sept in Harrogate between 6.30pm and 8.30pm. This is an opportunity for swimmers to shape the future of Masters swimming and swimmers from all backgrounds are encouraged to come and talk about this, therefore, Swim England are keen to hear from swimmers who would like to attend.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>If you are interested in attending then please contact National Masters Development Officer, Sharon Lock, on <a href="mailto:sharon.lock@swimming.org">sharon.lock@swimming.org</a></p>
<p style="font-style: italic;">Post expires at 9:42am on Saturday September 14th, 2019</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk/have-your-say-about-masters-swimming/">Have Your Say about Masters Swimming</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Swim England Tutor Training Opportunity</title>
		<link>http://asaner.org.uk/swim-england-tutor-training-opportunities-2/</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 21:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Daniel Ramm]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Swimming]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://asaner.org.uk/?p=18731</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>Swim England are currently looking for new coaching swimming tutors in the North East as well a number of other disciplines across the country. For more information and to request an application pack, please see here Applications close on the 16th August. Post expires at 9:28am on Monday August 19th, 2019</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk/swim-england-tutor-training-opportunities-2/">Swim England Tutor Training Opportunity</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Swim England are currently looking for new coaching swimming tutors in the North East as well a number of other disciplines across the country.</p>
<p>For more information and to request an application pack, please see <a href="https://www.swimming.org/swimengland/tutor-training-programme/">here</a></p>
<p>Applications close on the 16th August.</p>
<p style="font-style: italic;">Post expires at 9:28am on Monday August 19th, 2019</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk/swim-england-tutor-training-opportunities-2/">Swim England Tutor Training Opportunity</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Medals and a British Record at British Masters Championships for Northumberland and Durham Swimmers</title>
		<link>http://asaner.org.uk/medals-and-a-british-record-at-british-masters-championships-for-northumberland-and-durham-swimmers/</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 11:49:14 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Small]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Masters Swimming]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://asaner.org.uk/?p=18690</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>In June 2019, four Northumberland and Durham’s swimmers travelled to Swansea for the British Masters Championships. All of the swimmers had a fantastic meet achieving the following results: Will Jolly &#8211; Newcastle Swim Team Gold 400 metres and 800 metres Freestyle and a Silver in the 200 metres Freestyle. Verity Dobbie &#8211; Newcastle Swim Team [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk/medals-and-a-british-record-at-british-masters-championships-for-northumberland-and-durham-swimmers/">Medals and a British Record at British Masters Championships for Northumberland and Durham Swimmers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In June 2019, four Northumberland and Durham’s swimmers travelled to Swansea for the British Masters Championships. All of the swimmers had a fantastic meet achieving the following results:</p>
<p><strong>Will Jolly &#8211; Newcastle Swim Team</strong><br />
Gold 400 metres and 800 metres Freestyle and a Silver in the 200 metres Freestyle.</p>
<p><strong>Verity Dobbie &#8211; Newcastle Swim Team</strong><br />
Silver 50 metres Breaststroke and a New British record (the winner was from Norway), Silver in the 200 metres Breaststroke and Bronze in the 100 metres, 400 metres and 800 metres Freestyle.</p>
<p><strong>Ian Whyte &#8211; City of Sunderland </strong><br />
Silver in the 400 metres Freestyle.</p>
<p><strong>Joan Edwards &#8211; Gateshead and Whickham</strong><br />
Gold 400 metres and 800 metres Freestyle and Silver in the 100 metres and 200 metres Freestyle.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk/medals-and-a-british-record-at-british-masters-championships-for-northumberland-and-durham-swimmers/">Medals and a British Record at British Masters Championships for Northumberland and Durham Swimmers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jack Laugher Doubles Medal Tally in South Korea with Individual Bronze</title>
		<link>http://asaner.org.uk/jack-laugher-doubles-medal-tally-in-south-korea-with-individual-bronze/</link>
				<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2019 12:46:14 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Small]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Diving]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://asaner.org.uk/?p=18704</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>On Thursday 18th July, Olympic champion and Leeds based Jack Laugher doubled his medal tally at the 2019 World Aquatics Championships in South Korea, securing individual bronze to back up the synchro silver he won on Saturday. Whilst two medals and two Olympic Games places is a fantastic haul at any global championships, Jack will [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk/jack-laugher-doubles-medal-tally-in-south-korea-with-individual-bronze/">Jack Laugher Doubles Medal Tally in South Korea with Individual Bronze</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="article__aligner">
<div class="intro">
<div class="rich-text">
<p>On Thursday 18th July, Olympic champion and Leeds based Jack Laugher doubled his medal tally at the 2019 World Aquatics Championships in South Korea, securing individual bronze to back up the synchro silver he won on Saturday.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="streamfield">
<div class="article__aligner">
<div class="rich-text">
<p>Whilst two medals and two Olympic Games places is a fantastic haul at any global championships, Jack will rue a missed opportunity, as gold looked to be his until the last round. Leading throughout the competition, Jack had built a sizeable advantage over his Chinese rivals, but a final round error cost him his first World title.</p>
<p>Jack set his stall out from the word go, a high quality Front 2 ½ Somersault 2 Twist Pike (5154B) giving him an early lead, something he maintained through rounds two and three. The fireworks started in round four though, as Jack delivered a near perfect Front 2 ½ Somersaults 3 Twist Pike (5156B), which boasts a whopping 3.9 degrees of difficulty, the judges awarding it a huge 105.30 points.</p>
<p>Round five was just as good as Jack added 102.60 points to his tally with a sublime Front 4 ½ Somersaults Tuck (109C) putting him 31 points clear with a round to go. Unfortunately though it wasn’t to be, as he came out of his final dive fractionally too early meaning his bent legs slapped the water.</p>
<p>Despite the obvious disappointment, in time Jack will undoubtedly looked back on his first five dives very proudly and this will form a great platform as he heads into the Olympic Games next year, where he’ll look to match the gold and silver medals he won in Rio. For more on this story, <a href="https://www.britishswimming.org/news/diving-news/laugher-doubles-medal-tally-individual-bronze/?fbclid=IwAR1rZ65k3jOhcNHq49K74Wa7dCoc2KBKFYk_QeX2Wz7n8oasJIbnZFijFOI">please click here.</a></p>
<p><em>Picture Credit: British Swimming Twitter </em></p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk/jack-laugher-doubles-medal-tally-in-south-korea-with-individual-bronze/">Jack Laugher Doubles Medal Tally in South Korea with Individual Bronze</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coach 2024 Programme</title>
		<link>http://asaner.org.uk/coach-2024-programme/</link>
				<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2019 10:02:59 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[David Parry]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Clubs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Disability Swimming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Swimming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Workforce]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://asaner.org.uk/?p=18695</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>The Swim England Coach 2024 is an intensive 14 month learning journey for swimming coaches who aspire to excellence and coaching at world class levels. Further details including how to apply are available at: Swim England Coach 2024 Programme Post expires at 10:59am on Saturday August 10th, 2019</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk/coach-2024-programme/">Coach 2024 Programme</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Swim England Coach 2024 is an intensive 14 month learning journey for swimming coaches who aspire to excellence and coaching at world class levels.</p>
<p>Further details including how to apply are available at: <a href="https://www.swimming.org/sport/coach-2024-programme/">Swim England Coach 2024 Programme</a></p>
<p style="font-style: italic;">Post expires at 10:59am on Saturday August 10th, 2019</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk/coach-2024-programme/">Coach 2024 Programme</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Open Water Swimming &#8211; Important Information for Clubs</title>
		<link>http://asaner.org.uk/open-water-swimming-important-information-for-clubs/</link>
				<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 13:49:08 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Small]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Open Water Swimming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Open Water]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Swimming]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://asaner.org.uk/?p=18686</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>Please note the following information from Swim England regarding both clubs and individuals registering for Open Water Swimming. It is recommended that: Any club who has organised open water (ow) swimming activities should have a constitution that specifies it is doing open water swimming OR, uses the term aquatics (which covers ow swimming) in their [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk/open-water-swimming-important-information-for-clubs/">Open Water Swimming &#8211; Important Information for Clubs</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Please note the following information from Swim England regarding both clubs and individuals registering for Open Water Swimming. It is recommended that:</p>
<ol>
<li>Any club who has organised open water (ow) swimming activities should have a constitution that specifies it is doing open water swimming OR, uses the term aquatics (which covers ow swimming) in their constitution.</li>
<li>For those clubs that have got open water activities they should have ticked open water on their renewal submission.</li>
</ol>
<p>In the situation where a club has ticked open water in their renewal submission but none of their members have registered as open water swimmers, the club should make sure swimmers adjust their disciplines through OMS. If the club knows who is an open water swimmer they can do this throughout the year using the club OMS log in.</p>
<p>Please note, some swimmers will carry out open water training as individuals but not as part of a club activity. In this case the club should not be registered for open water swimming but the individual should be.</p>
<p>If you have any questions please contact either Swim England Membership <a href="mailto:renewals@swimming.org">renewals@swimming.org</a> or the Swim England Open Water Development Officer <a href="mailto:sharon.lock@swimming.org">sharon.lock@swimming.org</a>.</p>
<p>Please can you share this information with the appropriate people in your clubs.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk/open-water-swimming-important-information-for-clubs/">Open Water Swimming &#8211; Important Information for Clubs</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>World medal for Laugher and Goodfellow</title>
		<link>http://asaner.org.uk/world-medal-for-laugher-and-goodfellow/</link>
				<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 19:51:14 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Small]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Diving]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://asaner.org.uk/?p=18682</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>On Saturday, Leeds based Jack Laugher and Dan Goodfellow won Great Britain’s first medal of the 2019 World Aquatics Championships in South Korea, clinching silver in the Men’s 3m Synchro. Delivering a magnificent performance under immense pressure, the pair, who have only been working together for ten months, also secured Team GB a spot in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk/world-medal-for-laugher-and-goodfellow/">World medal for Laugher and Goodfellow</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On Saturday, Leeds based Jack Laugher and Dan Goodfellow won Great Britain’s first medal of the 2019 World Aquatics Championships in South Korea, clinching silver in the Men’s 3m Synchro.</p>
<div class="streamfield">
<div class="article__aligner">
<div class="rich-text">
<p>Delivering a magnificent performance under immense pressure, the pair, who have only been working together for ten months, also secured Team GB a spot in the event at next year’s Olympic Games in Tokyo. More on their fantastic result can be found here: <a href="https://www.britishswimming.org/news/diving-news/laugher-and-goodfellow-clinch-world-silver-and-olympic-berth/">British Swimming.</a></p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<p><em>Image: British Swimming Twitter</em></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk/world-medal-for-laugher-and-goodfellow/">World medal for Laugher and Goodfellow</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Swim England Invites Applications for New Officials</title>
		<link>http://asaner.org.uk/swim-england-invites-applications-for-new-officials/</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 10:45:26 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[David Parry]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Water Polo]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Workforce]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://asaner.org.uk/?p=18670</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>Swim England is inviting applications to help shape the structure of Water Polo officiating. More information is available here. Post expires at 11:38am on Saturday July 27th, 2019</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk/swim-england-invites-applications-for-new-officials/">Swim England Invites Applications for New Officials</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Swim England is inviting applications to help shape the structure of Water Polo officiating.</p>
<p>More information is available <a href="https://www.swimming.org/waterpolo/water-polo-officials/">here.</a></p>
<p style="font-style: italic;">Post expires at 11:38am on Saturday July 27th, 2019</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk/swim-england-invites-applications-for-new-officials/">Swim England Invites Applications for New Officials</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Places now available on Swimming Coach CPD Workshop in Sunderland</title>
		<link>http://asaner.org.uk/places-now-available-on-swimming-coach-cpd-workshop-in-sunderland/</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 13:25:01 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sarah Small]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Swimming]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://asaner.org.uk/?p=18659</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>A Starts,Turns, Finishes, Planning and Periodisation workshop has been organised to run at the Sunderland Aquatics Centre on Saturday 14th September, 2019, 10:00 &#8211; 15:00. The workshop will be led by Ryan Livingstone, Head Coach for Newcastle Swim Team and will include both poolside and classroom based teaching and learning. Places cost £15 per person [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk/places-now-available-on-swimming-coach-cpd-workshop-in-sunderland/">Places now available on Swimming Coach CPD Workshop in Sunderland</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Starts,Turns, Finishes, Planning and Periodisation workshop has been organised to run at the Sunderland Aquatics Centre on Saturday 14th September, 2019, 10:00 &#8211; 15:00.</p>
<p>The workshop will be led by Ryan Livingstone, Head Coach for Newcastle Swim Team and will include both poolside and classroom based teaching and learning.</p>
<p>Places cost £15 per person and can be booked and paid for through the regional website: <a href="http://asaner.org.uk/event/starts-turns-finishes-planning-periodisation/?fbclid=IwAR1F-6xSG_lWyP9hCqErdMIpTSKzTowUL6uElbTAKxRoh2okINiPewLsxkM">BOOK YOUR PLACE ON THE WORKSHOP HERE!</a></p>
<p>A flyer for the workshop can be found here: <a href="http://asaner.org.uk/mdocs-posts/startsturns-finishes-planning-periodisation-workshop-14th-september-2019/">Starts,Turns, Finishes, Planning and Periodisation Workshop 14th September 2019.</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p style="font-style: italic;">Post expires at 12:00am on Sunday September 15th, 2019</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk/places-now-available-on-swimming-coach-cpd-workshop-in-sunderland/">Places now available on Swimming Coach CPD Workshop in Sunderland</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://asaner.org.uk">Swim England North East</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
